so i'm not like fully versed on this so people in the comments please expound but i know the people
hi jedi i know the people are like why is trump so pressed about the trade of war moves without
being open if we have oil like why they keep acting like we don't got oil etc etc why are
they saying there's an oil shortage okay oil is attached to the u.s dollar the petra dollar
so oil being considered like the most valuable asset on the planet is attached to the dollar
which then makes the dollar valuable also remember in capitalism value is based on scarcity
so if you make something scarce even when it's in abundance if you just pretend it's scarce then you
make it more valuable there's plenty of diamonds everywhere but because they decided to make
diamonds valuable they then made scarcity you know who runs the diamond industry right
correct me if i'm wrong this is my understanding of it so that's why when they are selling oil and they
sell in the u.s dollar it gives the dollar value even though the dollar isn't backed by um gold so
the petra dollar has been what is literally like holding up our economy for quite some time now with
the street of war moves being closed it's not that we need oil it's that we need countries buying oil
in the petra dollar we need countries losing the petra dollar which is backed by the u.s dollar
we need countries using that economic exchange to make our economy valuable so the fact that you see
countries now buying oil in different currencies is the issue the reason why barack obama
and his administration took libya down was because gaddafi was trying to create a currency that was
backed by gold that would also lessen the value of the u.s dollar so all the so like majority of the
currencies around the world are literally supported by the u.s dollar in the sense that like their value
is attached to the u.s dollar but the u.s dollar isn't attached to anything because remember in the
70s they stopped having it backed by gold so all of it is fake and if they stop buying the oil in the
u.s dollar well then it really reveals the reality of the fakeness and then all these people whose
fortunes and all these countries who are propped up on this false concept collapse so that's how i
understand it can please can y'all in the comments tell me if i've got it right
behind the sea
i like your lesson